<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<content type="LES"><id>41</id>
<timestamp_x>1228916187</timestamp_x>
<date_create>1227877715</date_create>
<created_by>1</created_by>
<active>Y</active>
<course_id>4</course_id>
<chapter_id></chapter_id>
<name>Leave</name>
<sort>500</sort>
<preview_picture></preview_picture>
<preview_text></preview_text>
<preview_text_type>text</preview_text_type>
<detail_picture></detail_picture>
<detail_text><![CDATA[<b>Annual Leave</b>
<p>Annual leave can be used for whatever purposes you desire.  Most people use it for vacations and personal business.  Except for emergencies, annual leave must be authorized in advance by your supervisor.</p>  
<p>An employee accrues annual leave for each full pay period of employment unless he/she maintains a nonpay status for the entire pay period.  Annual leave is earned on the basis of the number of years of pfficial employment, including creditable military service if applicable.  The following table outlines the annual leave categories and the accrual rates for each:</p>
<p>Full-Time Employees:</p>
<table width="100%" cellpadding=0 cellspacing=0>
<tr bgcolor="white">
<td bgcolor="black">
<table width="100%" cellpadding=1 cellspacing=1>
	<tr bgcolor="white">
		<td width="50%">Less than 3 years of employment</td>
		<td width="25%">4 hour leave category</td>
		<td width="25%">13 days a year</td>
	</tr>
	<tr bgcolor="white">
		<td>3 serviceFrom 3 to 15 years of employment</td>
		<td>6 hour leave category</td>
		<td>20 days a year</td>
	</tr>
	<tr bgcolor="white">
		<td>15 years or more of employment</td>
		<td>8 hour leave category</td>
		<td>26 days a year</td>
	</tr>
</table>
</table>
<p>Part-Time Employees (One hour of leave is accrued for each):</p>
<table width="100%" cellpadding=0 cellspacing=0>
<tr bgcolor="white">
<td bgcolor="black">
<table width="100%" cellpadding=1 cellspacing=1>
	<tr bgcolor="white">
		<td width="60%">Less than 3 years of employment</td>
		<td width="40%">20 hours in pay status</td>
	</tr>
	<tr bgcolor="white">
		<td>From 3 to 15 years of employment</td>
		<td>13 hours in pay status</td>
	</tr>
	<tr bgcolor="white">
		<td>15 years or more of employment</td>
		<td>10 hours in pay status</td>
	</tr>
</table>
</table>

<p>Pay status hours which do not equal the number necessary for a minimum leave credit are carried over from one pay period to the next to accumulate toward future leave credits.  Employees can carry 30 days (240 hours) of unused annual leave from year to year.  You are advised to use your annual leave throughout the year in order to avoid losing accrued leave above the 30-day limit.</p>
<b>Sick Leave</b>
<p>Sick leave may be used when you: receive medical, dental, or optical examination or treatment; are incapacitated by physical or mental illness, injury, pregnancy, or childbirth; would, because of exposure to a communicable disease, jeopardize the health of others by your presence on the job; or must be absent from work for adoption-related activities.  In addition, you may use a limited amount of sick leave to: provide care for a family member as the result of physical or mental illness, injury,
pregnancy, childbirth, or medical, dental, or optical examination or treatment; or make arrangements necessitated by the death of a family member or attend the funeral of a family member.   For more information about Family Leave benefits, talk to your Supervisor and/or Human Resources.</p>
<p>For full-time employees, the sick leave accrual rate is 13 days a year; for part-time employees, it’s one hour for each 20 in pay status. There is no limit on how much can be accumulated.</p>
<p>There are other forms of leave including: compensatory time off; excused absences without loss of pay and without charge to leave; family and medical leave, seven days of paid leave each calendar year (in addition to annual or sick leave) to serve as a bone-marrow donor and 30 days to serve as an
organ donor; time off as a form of performance recognition; leave without pay used instead of paid leave for various purposes with supervisory approval; religious reasons, and military leave.</p>
]]></detail_text>
<detail_text_type>html</detail_text_type>
</content>