<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<content type="LES"><id>42</id>
<timestamp_x>1228916187</timestamp_x>
<date_create>1227877589</date_create>
<created_by>1</created_by>
<active>Y</active>
<course_id>4</course_id>
<chapter_id></chapter_id>
<name>Compensation</name>
<sort>550</sort>
<preview_picture></preview_picture>
<preview_text></preview_text>
<preview_text_type>text</preview_text_type>
<detail_picture></detail_picture>
<detail_text><![CDATA[<p>A pay range is established for each of the organization's jobs and these ranges are (a) internally
equitable, i.e., fair when compared with the ranges established for other Company jobs, as well as (b)
externally competitive when compared with the rates paid by other employers for comparable jobs.
Each employee whose performance is “proficient” or better will receive a rate of pay that falls within
the pay range that has been established for his/her job.
The position of each employee's salary within the range that has been established for his or her job
will be determined primarily by the employee's relevant experience and job performance.
Company’s compensation programs are designed and administered in such a way as to comply with all
applicable laws and to provide fair and equitable treatment for all employees.</p>
<b>Regular Pay Procedures</b>
<p>All Company employees are normally paid on Fridays on a bi-weekly basis. If a scheduled payday falls
on a company-observed holiday, you will usually be paid on the day preceding the holiday. All required
deductions, such as federal, state, and local taxes, and all authorized voluntary deductions, such as
health insurance contributions, will be withheld automatically from your paycheck.
All documentation of work completed must be submitted by those staff members providing direct patient care.</p>
<b>Merit Increases</b>
<p>The purpose of merit increases is to recognize and reward employee performance over a
designated period of time, and a minimum of once a year.</p>
<b>Acting Pay</b>
<p>Acting pay may be granted when an employee is temporarily assigned, for a period of at least one
(1) week or more, to assume a substantial portion of the responsibilities of a job with a higher pay
range.</p>
<b>Overtime</b>
<p>When a Company employee is required to work more than forty (40) hours in any given work week
(Company work week is regularly a seven day, 168 hour period) the following applicable overtime
pay policies will apply:</p>
<ul>
  <li>Non-exempt employees are to be paid one and one-half times their ‘regular hourly rate’ for all hours worked in excess of forty (40) hours in a workweek.</li>
  <li>Exempt employees are paid a salary commensurate with their job responsibilities regardless of the number of hours worked, and therefore are not eligible for overtime pay.</li>
</ul>
<b>On-Call Pay</b>
<p>Since some employees are required to be available for work on an on-call basis, special rates for
on-call hours will be paid to non-exempt employees. Your supervisor will notify you of proper
procedures if you are required to work on-call.</p>
<b>Bonus Pay</b>
<p>Bonus (and/or Incentive or Reward) Pay is additional compensation paid to an employee, or group
of employees, in addition to their normal rate of pay. Bonus pay may be granted only under limited
circumstances.</p>
<b>Market Adjustments</b>
<p>Market adjustments to salary ranges may occur outside of the annual Salary Planning cycle when
market demand has resulted in an increased rate of pay for a particular a job or job family.</p>
<b>Reductions In Pay</b>
<p>For a variety of reasons, an employee may be reassigned to a job that has a lower pay range than
the job they had previously held. In such cases, reduction in pay guidelines will apply.</p>
<b>Shift Differentials</b>
<p>Employees receive shift differential pay, for all hours worked, if they work a minimum of six (6)
consecutive hours during a shift where a differential applies.</p>
<b>Weekend Differentials</b>
<p>An employee who works four (4) or more consecutive hours during Company designated weekend
period is entitled to receive a weekend differential for all hours worked on that shift. For the
purposes of this policy, the weekend is defined as beginning 11:00 p.m. Friday and ending 7:00 a.m. Monday.</p>
<b>Unemployment Compensation</b>
<p>Our company  through the State Unemployment Compensation Act may provide you with income in
the event you become laid off or unemployed through no fault of your own. The entire cost of
this benefit is paid by the Company.</p>
]]></detail_text>
<detail_text_type>html</detail_text_type>
</content>